# SIMON STANCOVICH

### **PERSONLIGT**

Namn

Simon Stancovich

Adress

Mariehällsvägen 8 16866 Bromma

Telefonnummer

0734200137

E-post

simon.max.stancovich@gmail.com

#### HOBBYS

- Painting
- Studying new programming languages
- Gaming

## LANGUAGES

English
Spanish
Swedish

Passionate, perfectionist and super involved full-stack developer with many years of experience as a leader. I believe in team work and helping each other excel, there is something satisfying in watching people grow and the business you're in increase revenue as a result.

I'm a doer, and I love getting things done, I will never complain, I will always bring solutions.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Manager 2016 - 2020

Espresso house, Stockholm

Worked as the top manager at many top 40 units in Espresso House, I loved getting bad units that had terrible results, I turned every one of the numbers from red to green. I excel at inspiring everyone around me and getting things done with the help of my team, the more involved your team is the greater the sense of ownership they have and the greater the results!

## **District Manager Tr**

2020 - 2021

Espresso House, Stockholm

Helped train and educate managers in how to manage a unit to maximum profitability by inspiring and keeping every amazing employee.

## Tech lead / Full-Stack developer

2021 - 2022

Greater Than, Stockholm

Stack: Javascript, VueJS, Azure, C# & .net.

Worked developing solutions for insurance givers by making apps in VueJS.

Early in my career I started helping my team and everyone around me, quickly helping me evolve into a tech lead.

I work closely with my project manager to estimate deadlines.

I'm in charge of our educational program and helping our developers evolve and I'm in charge of our onboarding for new employees.

### **EDUCATION**

## .Net developer

2020 - 2022

TUC Sweden, Stockholm

Worked full time while getting my degree, fully examined with grade average of VG. (Highest score)

## **SKILLS**

Leadership		•	•	•	•
Problem solving	•	•	•	•	
Planning	•	•	•	•	•
VueJS	•	•	•	0	0
Javascript	•	•	0	0	0
MongoDB	•	•	0	0	0
NodeJS	•	•	0	0	0
C#	•	•	0	0	0
.net	•	0	0	0	0
ReactJS	•	0	0	0	0